[{"answer": "You know, when I went to London for the first time...", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Were the 80s as good fun for you as I always imagined they had to be?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "About you being pretty naughty in your past.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "When I sang that song I saw it as an opportunity to reach out to all young women and girls of every color and make a song about entitlement for women and in humor -- with humor and capture the people's imagination and color, capture the people's imagination and present an image of women that wasn't what was out there but more like the people that I knew that were the creative types and offer young women of all races an opportunity to see themselves in a different light.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "I mean, when you sang Girls Just Want To Have Fun, Cindy, what kind of fun at the time did you have in mind and how much of it did you actually help yourself to?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Ozone Park seems fitting.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Hell no -- heck no.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "ORGAN: Does that mean you're so engulfed with guilt for your bad behavior?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Oh, you don't -- I -- I ...", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "What did you do to get expelled?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "What did -- what did you do?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "...yes, this was number two.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "So this was number two?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "AUPER: Oh.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "What was number one?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "The first time, she said, you know, Cin, I didn't know -- well, you know, I was always singing anyway.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "What did your mother make of your career as it unfurled?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Yes, I like -- I -- there's some stuff I really like and I saw her do this thing when we doing the Viva Glam campaign where she did like a George Segal sculpture where she looked like a George Segal sculpture.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Are you a -- are you a Gaga fan?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Where is that?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "You think?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Nobody wants to hear you talk in any other way but like this.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Now, who -- who the heck is going to -- that's ridiculous, right?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Oh, all right.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Has all the hope that he came into power with evaporated?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Hon, I'm a woman and I know for a fact from day one, it don't matter what color you are, they blame the woman, it's her fault, all the time.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think it's as simple as that?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "I have a new name that you just gave me.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "I like the Big Shaqtus but which one of those do you particularly like?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "The Big Duke.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "It felt right.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "I mean, I know it probably wasn't the perfect scripted ending but do you feel inside you it's the time to go on?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Have you taken up golf yet?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "'NEAL: Well, you -- you used a wrong choice of words.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "I was like, what are they up to, these guys?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "You know, he's our president and, you know, I come from a military background and, you know, I'm all about respect and, you know, he does a -- he does a hard job.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What do you think of Obama?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I would say less, I mean, you know, Dr. Martin Luther King had this dream and the dream has finally come true and, you know, it's a hard job.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Do you think that having the first African American president has made America more or less racist?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I'm not sure.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What has happened to stop that kind of thing happening?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Yes, my mother was the driving force.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "You had this tough stepfather who I think you have great respect for but your mother, really, was the driving force, wasn't she, for allowing you, I guess, to -- to live a dream that you've now lived?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "It's very awful and, you know, my heart goes out to the, you know, victims' families.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "It's pretty awful isn't it what's been going on?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "I'm glad you understood that but when I was the leader Hershey and Blanchard states that leadership styles vary when you're dealing with task or relationships.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "You want to be better than them, I mean, unless I'm mistaken, it wasn't that you hated him, you just both wanted to be top dog, right?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I'm going to have to go with Michael Jordan but -- but, you know, I think sometimes that's an unfair question because the next guy that's coming in here, Magic Johnson, he was a great one too.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Who is the best player you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "...yes, that man right there.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "What I've always wondered about you is do you ever go out and people pick a fight with you?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Well, maybe a little bit but, you know, you know, people from seeing me on TV and, you know, from seeing me on Tout, they know that I'm a funny likable guy so if you say a crazy joke to me I'm going to say something back, we both laugh, we take a picture, and we move on.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Isn't it more to do with the fact that you're 7 feet tall and could pummel them to pieces?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "All of it.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What's been the greatest moment?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I've been blessed.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "How do you feel about still being around?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you take the drugs twice a day but I work out every day too and then, besides working out, taking your drugs, I -- I really believe is your frame of mind, how you deal with it, how you accept it and how you have to live with HIV and a lot of people don't accept it well so they don't do well.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "How -- how do you keep as healthy as you clearly appear to be?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "I think continue to help people to understand, this is -- this disease hasn't gone anywhere.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "What is the overriding message you would like to communicate on this particular anniversary?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, dealing with Shaq, Shaq is so amazing, he's probably -- I think he's been the most entertaining, most dominant player we've ever had and also great for the game.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "When you see Shaq, who has just retired after playing for the entire period since you retired, the 20 year period, do you wish, knowing what you know now, you hadn't retired when you did, do you wish you had carried on?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Well, I think that I was more shocked that the people who did support me because I think that at the end of the day, even when I wanted to come back to the NBA, a couple of players came out against me that they didn't want to play against me so I think that was the most shocking thing.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Were you more shocked by the people who supported you at the time who you didn't expect to or were you more disappointed by those you thought would who didn't?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I'm still mad today about that.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "That must have really annoyed you, didn't it?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Oh, no question about it.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "And if you're playing in a team -- a small team of people, and you're both touted by different sets of fans to be number one in the game, there's going to be rivalry isn't there?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Well, Michael Jordan was the best and, hands down, but, at the same time Bill Russell was the greatest winner.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Who's the best you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, he's the one I would love to play with because I would have a lot of assists playing with The Big Diesel but I think that Shaq, yes, you don't want to play against Shaq because not only was he big but also, too, he was light on his feet and he was probably the best passing big man -- him and Kareem were the two best passing big men that have ever played in the game.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "There can't be many worse moments in sports, are there?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Well, I think when we look back at it we wish it didn't happen from both the owner's side and the player's side.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Do you think it was ill advised that it ever happened at all in the current climate?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "All the time.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "How often do you think about it?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Not every day but all the time, you know, it's -- it's once a month or once every two weeks, you know, you think about it because I replay the games even now today.", "docId": "111203pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Every day?", "qSentId": 556}]